<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1" ?>
<rss version="2.0" 
   xmlns:creativeCommons="http://backend.userland.com/creativeCommonsRssModule" 
   xmlns:html="http://www.w3.org/1999/html" 
   xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" 
   xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/">
<channel>
   <title>Pyblosxom - main site</title>
   <link></link>
   <description>Pyblosxom project web-site</description>
   <language>en</language>
   <copyright></copyright>
   <ttl>60</ttl>
   <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2012 21:03 GMT</pubDate>
   <managingEditor>pyblosxom-users@lists.sourceforge.net</managingEditor>
   <generator>PyBlosxom http://pyblosxom.github.com/ 1.5.2</generator>
<item>
   <title>Handover and update</title>
   <guid isPermaLink="false">news/2012-06-27</guid>
   <link>/news/2012-06-27.</link>
   <description><![CDATA[
<p>
  After a significant number of years (since approx 2003) running PyBlosxom, willg has stepped down from managing the project and 
  passed it over to me, Akai.<br>
  will, thank you for your considerable effort in making PyBlosxom the program we know and love today.<br>
  <br>
  I'm available on the mailing lists and frequently on the IRC channel (as AkaiKitsune) for any question or issue I can help with.<br>
  Part of the handoff is the move from the bluesock.org domain to github for both the site and the repositories.<br>
  Update your bookmarks to http://pyblosxom.github.com/, that's our new home!
</p>

<p>
  -Akai
</p>

]]></description>
   <category domain=""></category>
   <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2012 21:03 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
   <title>Pyblosxom 1.5.2 released!</title>
   <guid isPermaLink="false">news/pyblosxom-1.5.2</guid>
   <link>/news/pyblosxom-1.5.2.</link>
   <description><![CDATA[
<p>This fixes two issues:</p>
<ol class="arabic simple">
<li>removed debug logging from pycategories</li>
<li>fixed a warning when doing <tt class="docutils literal">pip install pyblosxom</tt></li>
</ol>
<div class="section" id="where-to-get-it">
<h3>Where to get it</h3>
<p>We're pushing PyPI now.  To install Pyblosxom:</p>
<pre class="literal-block">
pip install pyblosxom
</pre>
<p>To upgrade:</p>
<pre class="literal-block">
pip install --upgrade pyblosxom
</pre>
<p>For tarballs, source code, and other things, see the website.</p>
</div>
<div class="section" id="how-to-get-help">
<h3>How to get help</h3>
<p>If you have any problems, say hi on IRC or send an email to the
pyblosxom-users mailing list.  Details are on <a class="reference external" href="http://pyblosxom.github.com/">the website</a>.</p>
</div>

]]></description>
   <category domain=""></category>
   <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2011 01:15 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
   <title>Pyblosxom 1.5.1 released!</title>
   <guid isPermaLink="false">news/pyblosxom-1.5.1</guid>
   <link>/news/pyblosxom-1.5.1.</link>
   <description><![CDATA[
<p>This fixes two issues:</p>
<ol class="arabic simple">
<li>manifest was missing README.rst which hosed <tt class="docutils literal">python setup.py install</tt></li>
<li>the WHATSNEW page had the wrong version and date for the 1.5 release</li>
</ol>
<p>The first is bad and worth putting out a new release.  Sorry about
that.  Many thanks to ntoll who popped on IRC and let us know.</p>
<div class="section" id="where-to-get-it">
<h3>Where to get it</h3>
<p>We're pushing PyPI now.  To install Pyblosxom:</p>
<pre class="literal-block">
pip install pyblosxom
</pre>
<p>To upgrade:</p>
<pre class="literal-block">
pip install --upgrade pyblosxom
</pre>
<p>For tarballs, source code, and other things, see the website.</p>
</div>
<div class="section" id="how-to-get-help">
<h3>How to get help</h3>
<p>If you have any problems, say hi on IRC or send an email to the
pyblosxom-users mailing list.  Details are on <a class="reference external" href="http://pyblosxom.github.com/">the website</a>.</p>
</div>

]]></description>
   <category domain=""></category>
   <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2011 00:22 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
   <title>Pyblosxom 1.5 final released</title>
   <guid isPermaLink="false">news/pyblosxom-1.5</guid>
   <link>/news/pyblosxom-1.5.</link>
   <description><![CDATA[
<div class="section" id="release">
<h3>Release!</h3>
<p>It's been a long road for Pyblosxom 1.5.  The first time I said that
PyBlosxom 1.5 was pretty much done was in June of 2009.  That turned
out to be hilariously wrong and development continued for another two
and a half years.</p>
<p>In that period of time, we switched from svn to git and put the
project on Gitorious, we switched bug trackers, we had like 350
commits, we added tests, we started using a wiki, we abandoned the
wiki, we renamed the project, we overhauled the documentation a few
times, we added plugins, we removed plugins, we did the hokey-pokey
and moved the rest of them around a few times, we moved the project to
GitHub, we started using IRC more heavily, we had three release
candidates, and a bunch of other things.</p>
<p>Was Pyblosxom 1.5 worth it?  Definitely---it's a magnificent
improvement over 1.4.3.  I highly recommend upgrading.</p>
<p>For complete details of what's new in 1.5, read the <a class="reference external" href="http://pyblosxom.github.com/1.5/whatsnew.html">WHATSNEW section
of the manual</a>.
Here are some highlights:</p>
<ol class="arabic simple">
<li>We changed the name of the project to Pyblosxom.  Down with camel case.</li>
<li>Plugins are now part of the package.  When you upgrade Pyblosxom in
the future, core plugins will automatically get upgraded, too.
Plugin documentation is now part of the manual.  There are some new
plugins, some rewritten plugins, and a bunch of plugins have seen
significant improvements.</li>
<li>pyblosxom-cmd is vastly improved.  Creating a new blog is much
easier than in previous versions.</li>
<li>Better crash handling.  Pyblosxom now has a crash page that makes
it easier to figure out why it's crashing and either fix it or tell
someone the information they need to know to fix it.</li>
<li>Improved documentation.</li>
<li>Vastly cleaner code, more tests, and better project infrastructure.</li>
<li>More options for static rendering.</li>
</ol>
<p>Yay for Pyblosxom 1.5!</p>
</div>
<div class="section" id="where-to-get-it">
<h3>Where to get it</h3>
<p>We're pushing PyPI now.  To install Pyblosxom:</p>
<pre class="literal-block">
pip install pyblosxom
</pre>
<p>To upgrade:</p>
<pre class="literal-block">
pip install --upgrade pyblosxom
</pre>
<p>For tarballs, source code, and other things, see the website.</p>
</div>
<div class="section" id="how-to-get-help">
<h3>How to get help</h3>
<p>If you have any problems, say hi on IRC or send an email to the
pyblosxom-users mailing list.  Details are on <a class="reference external" href="http://pyblosxom.github.com/">the website</a>.</p>
</div>

]]></description>
   <category domain=""></category>
   <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2011 01:24 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
   <title>Status December 12th, 2011</title>
   <guid isPermaLink="false">news/2011-12-12</guid>
   <link>/news/2011-12-12.</link>
   <description><![CDATA[
<p>It's been a while since the last status update and a lot has happened
since then:</p>
<ul class="simple">
<li>renamed the project from PyBlosxom to Pyblosxom</li>
<li>folded core plugins into the Pyblosxom core</li>
<li>moved the pyblosxom repository from gitorious to github</li>
<li>added new plugins, bug fixes, more tests, fixed documentation, ...</li>
</ul>
<p>We're pretty close to a 1.5 final release.  This release has been a long time
coming and it'll be good to get it out.  I'm hoping it'll happen in the next
week.</p>

]]></description>
   <category domain=""></category>
   <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 18:38 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
   <title>PyBlosxom 1.5rc3 released</title>
   <guid isPermaLink="false">news/pyblosxom-1.5rc3</guid>
   <link>/news/pyblosxom-1.5rc3.</link>
   <description><![CDATA[
<p>
  We did 1.5 rc2 10 months ago.  Since then we've added a few new plugins,
  fixed a bunch of bugs, worked on making the documentation better, updated
  docstrings, and some other stuff.
</p>
<p>
  There are still a bunch of polish things that need to be done, so we're
  going to do another release candidate.
</p>
<p>
  Download the new version at 
  <a href="/download/pyblosxom-1.5rc3.tar.gz">pyblosxom-1.5rc3.tag.gz</a>.
</p>
<p>
  If you have any problems, say hi on IRC (<code>#pyblosxom</code>
  on <code>irc.freenode.net</code>), send an email to the pyblosxom-users 
  mailing list, or send me an email at <code>willg at bluesock dot org</code>.
</p>
<p>
/will (willg at bluesock dot org)
</p>

]]></description>
   <category domain=""></category>
   <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2011 03:06 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
   <title>Status March 19th, 2011</title>
   <guid isPermaLink="false">news/2011-03-19</guid>
   <link>/news/2011-03-19.</link>
   <description><![CDATA[
<p>
  We've done a ton of work over the last 3 and a half months.  One thing
  that I finally got around to was overhauling the web-site.  The new
  web-site is (I think) a lot better, more informative, and easier to
  use.
</p>
<p>
  Things that still need to be done:
</p>
<ol>
<li>update the plugin registry
<li>update the flavour registry
<li>compile the 1.5 documentation and push that to the site
</ol>
<p>
  There are still a series of outstanding tasks for PyBlosxom 1.5 that should
  get finished before we release 1.5 final.  We're working on them.  We
  could use your help!
</p>
<ul>
<li>check PyBlosxom 1.5 in git to see if it works with your blog and plugins
<li>run the unit tests
<li>edit and update documentation
<li>triage and fix bugs in the 1.5 milestone in the bug tracker
</ul>
<p>
  We just finished up a sprint week and we're eager to finish up 1.5 and
  get it out.  Hopefully, we'll get that done in the next week or two.
</p>
<p>
  /will (willg at bluesock dot org)
</p>

]]></description>
   <category domain=""></category>
   <pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2011 21:03 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
   <title>Status January 8th, 2011</title>
   <guid isPermaLink="false">news/2011-01-08</guid>
   <link>/news/2011-01-08.</link>
   <description><![CDATA[
<p>
  Development slowed down during the second half of 2010 because I was
  bogged down with other things.  I recognize how that totally sucks
  for the project.  I'm working on rectifying it now.
</p>
<p>
  Previously, we were using the SF bug tracker which sucked.  Since
  we did much with it, it's undergone a user interface overhaul and it's
  better, but it's still missing features this project needs.  So we
  stopped using it and I directed people to file bug reports by sending
  email to the pyblosxom-devel mailing list.
</p>
<p>
  In October of 2010, we discussed issue trackers.  Then I went on
  hiatus for a little over a month.  I've returned now and set up Roundup
  to host PyBlosxom issues and feature requests.  With help from Asheesh
  and the awesome folks at <a href="http://openhatch.org">OpenHatch</a>
  I added support for tracking milestones.  I've moved all open bugs
  and features from the SF bug tracker to the new bug tracker.
</p>
<p>
  You can find it at <a href="http://pyblosxom.bluesock.org/bugs/">http://pyblosxom.bluesock.org/bugs/</a>.
</p>
<p>
  I also got through the queue of merge requests from Dieter.  I
  really apologize for sitting on those for so long.  I really appreciate
  the work he did on them.
</p>
<p>
  I want to move ahead and get a PyBlosxom 1.5 rc3 out soon.  We're still
  fixing problems in plugins and working on getting PyBlosxom and the core
  plugins to a stable state--hence the need for ongoing release candidates
  rather than a final release.
</p>
<p>
  I want to thank Dieter for his prodding.  Also, Tim, Marius, Bill, Michael,
  Glennie, Sean, Sebastian, and Asheesh for their participation, efforts, 
  thoughts, and other positive energy things on #miro-hackers and the
  pyblosxom-devel list.  I'm looking forward to the rest of 2011, cleaning
  up the project and making it better for everyone.
</p>
<p>
  /will (willg at bluesock dot org)
</p>

]]></description>
   <category domain=""></category>
   <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2011 17:35 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
   <title>PyBlosxom 1.5rc2 released</title>
   <guid isPermaLink="false">news/pyblosxom-1.5rc2</guid>
   <link>/news/pyblosxom-1.5rc2.</link>
   <description><![CDATA[
<p>
  It's been about 6 months since 1.5 rc1.  Since then we've been updating
  plugins, added some new plugins, adding tests, fixed documentation, 
  added a sortlist callback, updated docstrings, switched from subversion
  to git, moved from SourceForge to Bluesock, and some other stuff.
</p>
<p>
  Doing another release candidate because there's still a lot of work to
  do updating plugins, adding tests, and fixing documentation.
</p>
<p>
  Download the new version at 
  <a href="/download/pyblosxom-1.5rc2.tar.gz">pyblosxom-1.5rc2.tag.gz</a>.
</p>
<p>
  If you have any problems, say hi on IRC (<code>#pyblosxom</code>
  on <code>irc.freenode.net</code>), send an email to the pyblosxom-users 
  mailing list, or send me an email at <code>willg at bluesock dot org</code>.
</p>
<p>
/will (willg at bluesock dot org)
</p>

]]></description>
   <category domain=""></category>
   <pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2010 14:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
   <title>New site, new conventions, almost new version</title>
   <guid isPermaLink="false">news/2010-04-17</guid>
   <link>/news/2010-04-17.</link>
   <description><![CDATA[
<p>
  We're moving from SourceForge to Bluesock.  Bluesock is my own personal
  server where I'll have a lot more control over the site in terms of how
  it's built.  On SourceForge we're severely limited to static pages or
  the various applications that they install.  It's been a real pain in
  the ass.
</p>
<p>
  Additionally, I've gone through the site and updated it to reflect our
  move from svn to git.
</p>
<p>
  On top of that, we're ditching the SourceForge bug tracker.  We don't
  have a bug tracker set up, though, so we're just going to wing it with
  the pyblosxom-devel mailing list.  If it becomes necessary, we'll set
  up a new bug tracker.
</p>
<p>
  PyBlosxom 1.5 is almost done.  A handful of things have been done since
  the release candidate a while back.  The documentation still needs another
  going over and parts of it need to be updated.
</p>
<p>
  Hopefully all that will happen soon.
</p>
<p>
  /will
</p>

]]></description>
   <category domain=""></category>
   <pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2010 21:50 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
